<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<page>
	<content-type>/page/enpagechinhsach</content-type>
	<display-template>/templates/web/pages/en/chinhsach.ftl</display-template>
	<no-template-required/>
	<merge-strategy>inherit-levels</merge-strategy>
	<objectGroupId>51eca327</objectGroupId>
	<objectId>51eca327-7929-4bb3-ba66-b951b15678cd</objectId>
	<file-name>index.xml</file-name>
	<folder-name>2</folder-name>
	<internal-name>Corporate culture</internal-name>
	<navLabel>Corporate culture</navLabel>
	<title_s>Corporate culture</title_s>
	<placeInNav>false</placeInNav>
	<orderDefault_f>-1</orderDefault_f>
	<image_s>/static-assets/images/tuyen-dung/5O6A7027.JPG</image_s>
	<slide_o item-list="true">	<item datasource="slide" inline="true">	<key>4712d73f-e76b-eb2b-db99-908ef3c59174</key>
	<value>S</value>
<component id="4712d73f-e76b-eb2b-db99-908ef3c59174">
	<content-type>/component/slide</content-type>
	<display-template>/templates/web/components/slide.ftl</display-template>
	<no-template-required/>
	<merge-strategy>inherit-levels</merge-strategy>
	<objectGroupId>4712</objectGroupId>
	<objectId>4712d73f-e76b-eb2b-db99-908ef3c59174</objectId>
	<file-name>4712d73f-e76b-eb2b-db99-908ef3c59174.xml</file-name>
	<internal-name>S</internal-name>
	<image_s>/static-assets/images/header/bg-app1.jpg</image_s>
	<createdDate>2021-10-06T07:52:40.092Z</createdDate>
	<createdDate_dt>2021-10-06T07:52:40.092Z</createdDate_dt>
	<lastModifiedDate>2021-10-06T07:52:40.092Z</lastModifiedDate>
	<lastModifiedDate_dt>2021-10-06T07:52:40.092Z</lastModifiedDate_dt>
</component>
	</item></slide_o>
	<content_html>&lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;Mavin group is the convergence of all the elite individual of Vietnam and International, those who are passionate about the development of Vietnam Agribusiness, with a very simple dream of providing a safe, hygienic food source for the people and the sake of their health.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;6 core values include &amp;ldquo;Unity - Innovation &amp;ndash; Responsibily &amp;ndash; Quality &amp;ndash; Customer satisfaction &amp;ndash; Transparency&amp;rdquo; are currently the guidance for all the operation of Mavin. With over 15 years of experience, Mavin is proud to be one of the most trustworthy and prestigious enterprise in providing the &amp;ldquo;From Farm the Table&amp;rdquo; supply chain to people, and to provide clean and fully traceable products from their sources to each and every Vietnamese consumers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;The working spirit of Responsibility and Innovation is flowing strongly inside each and every Mavin staff. Each innovative and renovated idea that utilize procedure and process for higher productivity, effectiveness, efficiency is well received by the Management Board and is well rewarded with the total fund for innovative reaching $10,000 a year. 5S Spirit is promoted throughout, contribute greatly in increasing the efficiency and effectiveness if Mavin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;Product quality and customer satisfaction is the final goal in Mavin&amp;rsquo;s supply chain, is the basis and driving force for all Mavin staffs to complete themselves. We always treasure and honor the relationship with the customers, listen and understand the needs of the customer to constantly improve products quality and customer experience. All Mavin staffs are well trained on customer service skills and always put quality and customer experience as the top two factors needed for the sustainable development of Mavin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;In order that every staff is able to share their goals and plans, Mavin regularly organise annual Team Building&amp;nbsp; programs for all sales staff and Strategic Business Seminar for management. Internal forums, newsletters.... are where staffs update information, exchange knowledge and experience, which all contribute to the united and transparency spirit in Mavin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;Mavin is proud to be the second home to staff, where each of its members is closely attached and spend their time in it following their passions to develop. Mavin is also proud of all the highly qualified experts and technicians in Agriculture and Food who were trained in Mavin, and day by day have been contributing greatly to the development of Mavin as well as the development of Agriculture of Vietnam.&lt;/p&gt;</content_html>
	<createdDate>2021-10-06T07:52:19.547Z</createdDate>
	<createdDate_dt>2021-10-06T07:52:19.547Z</createdDate_dt>
	<lastModifiedDate>2021-11-08T01:47:56.580Z</lastModifiedDate>
	<lastModifiedDate_dt>2021-11-08T01:47:56.580Z</lastModifiedDate_dt>
	<date_dt>2021-10-06T04:00:00.000Z</date_dt>
	<date_dt_tz>EST5EDT</date_dt_tz>
</page>